{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "suuid": "82Js23",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "how to find out your Linux shell",
      "back": "echo $0"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "2Jjq4a",
      "category": "git",
      "front": "get back file from staging area to working directory, i.e. unstage a file",
      "back": "git reset [file]"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "891As1",
      "category": "git",
      "front": "show commit history with hash, title, author",
      "back": "git log --pretty=format:\"%h - %s - %an\" "
    },
    {
      "suuid": "3bCd45",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "navigate to the home directory",
      "back": "cd ~"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "7iJk89",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "create a new file",
      "back": "touch index.html"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "IircrT",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "111",
      "back": "222"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "HyLnqk",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "444",
      "back": "555"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "UB65OT",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "666",
      "back": "777"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "DQCFTo",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdf",
      "back": "dfdf"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "YPTT9I",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdf",
      "back": "dfdf"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "sKbDJN",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdf",
      "back": "ddfdf"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "5IyP71",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdfd",
      "back": "dfdf"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "8HSK8U",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdfd",
      "back": "dfdf"
    },
    {
      "suuid": "AwPkGx",
      "category": "linux",
      "front": "dfdfd",
      "back": "dfdf"
    }
  ]
}